export default {
  title: "ㄱ ㄲ ㅋ",
  syllables: [
    {
      question: '기',
      answer: 'ㄱ',
      options: "ㄱ ㄲ ㅋ",
    }, {
      question: '끼',
      answer: 'ㄲ',
      options: "ㄱ ㄲ ㅋ",
    }, {
      question: '키',
      answer: 'ㅋ',
      options: "ㄱ ㄲ ㅋ",
    }, {
      question: '겁',
      answer: 'ㄱ',
      options: "ㄱ ㄲ ㅋ",
    }, {
      question: '껍',
      answer: 'ㄲ',
      options: "ㄱ ㄲ ㅋ",
    }, {
      question: '컵',
      answer: 'ㅋ',
      options: "ㄱ ㄲ ㅋ",
    }, {
      question: '글',
      answer: 'ㄱ',
      options: "ㄱ ㄲ ㅋ",
    }, {
      question: '끌',
      answer: 'ㄲ',
      options: "ㄱ ㄲ ㅋ",
    }, {
      question: '클',
      answer: 'ㅋ',
      options: "ㄱ ㄲ ㅋ",
    }, {
      question: '고',
      answer: 'ㄱ',
      options: "ㄱ ㄲ ㅋ",
    }, {
      question: '꼬',
      answer: 'ㄲ',
      options: "ㄱ ㄲ ㅋ",
    }, {
      question: '코',
      answer: 'ㅋ',
      options: "ㄱ ㄲ ㅋ",
    }
  ]
}
